字幕：Hongjiang399     微信：Hongjiang399
如果你是Lynda.com在线培训课程的会员，或者你
If you are a premium member of the lynda.com Online Training Library or if you
在光盘上观看本课程，你将会找到
are watching this course on a disc, you'll have access to the Exercise Files
随课程的练习文件
that are delivered with the course.
我已把练习文件复制到桌面，你可以把文件放到你电脑中的任何位置
I've copied the Exercise Files to my Desktop, but you can place them anywhere on your system.
练习文件包含了一系列的Java工程文件
The Exercise Files for this course consists of a set of Java project files built
均由Eclipse软件创建，但文件中的源代码能用于
for use in Eclipse, but the source code in these project files can be used in
任何Java开发环境当中
any Java development environment.
我电脑中有一个名为.metadata的文件
On my system there is a file named .metadata.
如果你还没开启Eclipse你不会看到这个文件，但
You won't see it on your system if you haven't opened Eclipse yet, but it will
一旦你做本课程的练习这个文件将会被自动创建
be created automatically as you work through the course's exercises.
每一章对应练习文件中的一个文件夹
Each chapter is represented by a folder in the main Exercise Files folder.
例如第03章有4个子文件夹
So for example Chapter 03 has a set of four subfolders.
每个子文件夹均为一个Eclipse工程
Each of these subfolders is an Eclipse project.
例如名为APIDocs的文件夹包含有
For example the APIDocs folder contains an Eclipse project for learning
用于学习API文档的Eclipse工程
about API documentation.
在文件夹内你能看到包含Java源程序的src文件夹
Within this folder you'll see a source folder that contains the actual Java
以及一个bin文件夹，对应被编译过的可执行文件
source code and a bin folder where the application is being compiled.
如果你用的是Windows系统，你同时会看到.classpath和.project两个文件
If you are working on Windows you'll also see these two files .classpath and .project.
这些文件是由Eclipse所生成的，用于配置
These are files that are generated by Eclipse and that are used to configure
对应的Eclipse工程
the Eclipse project.
如果你用的是Mac系统，你可能看不到这些文件，但它们仍然存在
If you are working on Mac you might not see these files in Finder but they are still there.
下面介绍如何使用每个工程文件
Here is how you use each project.
我打开Eclipse，在随后课程中我将会展示如何安装这个软件
I'll open Eclipse, which I'll show you how to install very early in the
我向你展示在这个Eclipse中我已经打开了4个工程文件
course, and I'll show you that in this copy of Eclipse I already have four projects open.
我将导入另一个工程文件
Now I am going to import another project.
在菜单栏中我选择File->Import->Existing Projects into Workspace
From the menu I'll choose File> Import>Existing Projects into Workspace.
我点击Browse并找到我的练习文件夹
I'll click Browse and navigate to my Exercise Files.
若我选择这个文件夹作为根目录，那么我会看到所有工程文件
If I choose this folder as my root folder I'll see all available projects
整个文件夹包含了课程所有刚开始的工程以及
throughout the entire folder including all of the beginning projects and all of
所有解决方案工程
the solution projects.
另一方法：你也可以导入其中一章的工程
Alternatively you might decide you just want to import one chapter's worth of projects.
我选择了第4章Primitives，现在我看到了短得多的文件列表
I'll choose 04_Primitives and now I'll see a much shorter list.
或者你也可以只导入单独一个工程
Or you can choose to import just a single project.
这次我选择了第4章Primitives->Booleans，并点击OK，我就只看见
This time I'll choose 04_Primitives> Booleans and click OK, and I'll see only the
属于此文件夹的一个工程
project in that folder.
无论你导入单独一个工程、一整章或者课程的所有工程
Whether you import one project at a time or a whole chapter or all the projects
这都取决于你自己
for the entire course it's completely up to you.
当你完成了一个工程，我建议你至少要关闭它，或者
When you are done with a project I recommend that you at least close it or
你也可以在Eclipse中删除它
optionally delete it from Eclipse.
关闭工程只需要右击工程列表的工程并选择关闭
To close a project right-click on it in the Package Explorer and close the project.
如果你想完全退出工程，只需要选择工程
If you prefer to get rid of the project completely just select the project
然后按下删除
folder and press Delete.
你将会被提示从Eclipse工作空间中删除工程
You'll be prompted to remove the project from the Eclipse workspace.
不要选这个选项，这样工程文件将依然保存在硬盘中
Don't check this option and then the project will still be there on disc.
如果你选了这个选项，那么你实际上不仅删除了工程而且还
If you do check the option you are actually deleting the project and all of
删除了位于硬盘上的源代码，那样你就需要从练习文件中重新解压出来了
its source code from the disc and you'll have to extract it from the Exercise Files again.
这就是怎么使用本课程的练习文件的方法
So that's a look at how to work with the exercise files for this course.
如果你无法获取练习文件，那么你可以使用你自己的Java源代码
If you don't have access to the Exercise Files you can use your own Java code.
本课程的每个视频中我会展示我正编写的所有代码
In each video in the course I'll show you all of the code that I am working with.
因此你可以复制视频中的代码到你的应用中，或者你也可以创建
So you can either copy that code into your application or you can create
你自己的代码并随之开始学习Java编程语言
your own custom code as you begin the process of learning the Java programming language.
字幕GitHub: https://github.com/Hongjiang399/JavaEssentialTrainingSRT.git